<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="105">
    <author>NX Modding</author>
    <version>1.0.0.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>Productions Manager</en>
        <de>Produktionsmanager</de>
        <fr>Gestionnaire De Production</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[Comprehensive production management system for Farming Simulator 25.

Features:
• Production Overview: View all productions with fill levels, capacities, and monthly income
• Toggle Views: Switch between inputs, outputs, and recipes
• Financial Tracking: See monthly revenue, costs, and net profit for each production
• Logistics Page: Overview of all production's and their recipies includes, Supply Duration, Cycles/MO, Output Mode, Location, Status
• Production Scheduling: Set active months per recipe — productions outside their scheduled months are automatically paused and resumed.
• Auto-Management: Automatically activate/deactivate productions based on input availability and output capacity
• Smart Notifications: Get alerts when productions stop/start or when inputs are low/outputs are high
• CSV Export: Export all production data for external analysis
• Multi-Language Support: Available in 3 languages

Press Right Shift + P to open the Production Overview.

Logo: MarkThor
]]></en>

        <de><![CDATA[Umfassendes Produktionsverwaltungssystem für Landwirtschafts-Simulator 25.

Funktionen:
• Produktionsübersicht: Alle Produktionen mit Füllständen, Kapazitäten und monatlichem Einkommen anzeigen
• Ansichten umschalten: Zwischen Eingängen, Ausgängen und Rezepten wechseln
• Logistikverfolgung: Ausgabezyklen, Standort, Status, Rezeptname und Verteilungsziel anzeigen
• Finanzverfolgung: Monatliche Einnahmen, Kosten und Nettogewinn jeder Produktion anzeigen
• Produktionsplanung: Aktive Monate pro Rezept festlegen — außerhalb des Zeitplans werden Produktionen automatisch pausiert.
• Automatische Verwaltung: Produktionen basierend auf Eingangsverfügbarkeit und Ausgangskapazität automatisch aktivieren/deaktivieren
• Intelligente Benachrichtigungen: Warnungen erhalten, wenn Produktionen stoppen/starten oder wenn Eingaben niedrig/Ausgaben hoch sind
• CSV-Export: Alle Produktionsdaten für externe Analyse exportieren
• Mehrsprachige Unterstützung: In 3 Sprachen verfügbar

Drücken Sie Rechte Umschalttaste + P, um die Produktionsübersicht zu öffnen.

Logo: MarkThor
]]></de>

        <fr><![CDATA[Système complet de gestion des productions pour Farming Simulator 25.

Fonctionnalités:
• Aperçu des productions: Visualisez toutes les productions avec niveaux de remplissage, capacités et revenus mensuels
• Basculer les vues: Basculez entre entrées, sorties et recettes
• Suivi logistique: Consultez les cycles de sortie, emplacement, statut, nom de la recette et destination de distribution
• Suivi financier: Consultez les revenus mensuels, coûts et bénéfice net de chaque production
• Planification des productions: Définissez les mois actifs par recette — les productions hors planning sont automatiquement suspendues
• Gestion automatique: Active/désactive automatiquement les productions en fonction de la disponibilité des entrées et de la capacité de sortie
• Notifications intelligentes: Recevez des alertes lorsque les productions s'arrêtent/démarrent ou lorsque les entrées sont faibles/sorties élevées
• Export CSV: Exportez toutes les données de production pour analyse externe
• Support multilingue: Disponible en 3 langues

Appuyez sur Maj Droite + P pour ouvrir l'aperçu des productions.

Logo: MarkThor
]]></fr>
    </description>
    
    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n"/>
    <iconFilename>icon_ProductionsOverview.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="ProductionOverview.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="RegisterPlayerActionEvents.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="core/ProductionNotifications.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="core/ProductionSettings.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="core/ProductionAutoManager.lua" />
        <sourceFile filename="core/ProductionScheduleManager.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
    <actions>
        <action name="SHOW_PRODUCTION_DLG" category="SYSTEM" />
    </actions>  
    <inputBinding>
        <actionBinding action="SHOW_PRODUCTION_DLG">
            <binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rshift KEY_p" />
        </actionBinding>
    </inputBinding> 
</modDesc>
